FRIMPONG DANIEL

Techiman, Bono East / +233 (0) 556079013 / danillefrimpong77@gmail.com

PROFILE STATEMENT

I am highly organized and detail-oriented Data Entry Specialist with a 3-year experience in accurately and efficiently entering data into various systems. Seeking a position where I can utilize my strong attention to detail and data management skills to contribute to the success of the organization.

EDUCATION

BSc. Computer Engineering / January 2023

University of Energy and Natural Resources, Sunyani - Ghana

Major Courses: Data Structures and Algorithms, Computer Networking, Software Engineering, Digital Logic Design.

General Science

Techiman Senior High School / October 2018 - August 2021

SKILLS

- Proficient in data entry and data entry processing software
- Excellent typing speed and accuracy
- Strong attention to detail and ability to maintain data integrity
- Familiarity with database management systems
- Strong organizational and time management skills
- Effective communication and teamwork abilities

WORK EXPERIENCE

- Data Entry Specialist (Theresah Care Educational Complex), Techiman / September 2021 - December 2021
- Data Entry Intern (Premium Pharmacy), Techiman / January 2022 - September 2022
- Typist Intern
 (iTech Solutions) Sunyani / October 2023 December 2023

REFERENCE

Kyei Donkor Abraham Headmaster Theresah Care Educational Complex Techiman, Bono East +233 (0) 558349642 Adu Yeboah Joseph C.E.O Premium Pharmacy Techiman, Bono East +233 (0) 494995283